joinhomebase.com 2019-05-19

# Homebase - Privacy

### Privacy Policy

Last Revision: July 11, 2018

### Our Policy:

Welcome to the web site (the  **“Site”** ) of Pioneer Works, Inc. (“Pioneer Works”, “we”, “us” and/or “our”). This Site is operated by Pioneer Works and has been created to provide information about our company and our services provided under the name “Homebase” and related technologies. This Privacy Policy sets forth Pioneer Works policy with respect to information including personally identifiable data ( **“Personal Data”** ) and other information that is collected from visitors to the Site and Services. 

### Information We Collect:

When you interact with us through the Services, we may collect Personal Data and other information from you, as further described below. 

We collect Personal Data from you when you voluntarily provide such information, such as when you contact us with inquiries, respond to one of our surveys, register for access to the Services or use certain Services. The information we collect includes unique identifiers, browser type and settings, device type and settings, operating system, mobile network information including carrier name and phone number, and application version number. We also collect information about the interaction of your apps, browsers, and devices with our services, including IP address, crash reports, system activity, and the date, time, and referrer URL of your request. We may also collect information about your location when you use our services, which helps us offer features mobile time clock usage or alerts for scheduled shifts or breaks or other jobs that might be nearby and of interest to you. Wherever Pioneer Works collects Personal Data we make an effort to provide a link to this Privacy Policy. We may collect personally identifiable information about you, such as your full name, phone number, email address, or similar, when you register for an account. If you choose to purchase a product from us, we or our third-party payment processors will collect your payment information. When you use our Services or if you visit our websites, we may receive certain information about you as described below. We may send promotional emails from time to time that apply to your account and we may send you service related emails related to your account. If you no longer wish to receive these emails, you may opt out of them or cancel your account. 

By voluntarily providing us with Personal Data, you are consenting to our use of it in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you provide Personal Data to the Services, you acknowledge and agree that such Personal Data may be transferred from your current location to the offices and servers of Pioneer Works or the authorized third parties referred to herein located in the United States. The security of your Personal Information is important to us, and we implement and maintain reasonable, commercially acceptable security procedures and practices in order to protect it from unauthorized access, use, modification, or disclosure. Our measures include firewalls, data encryption, SSL encryption, physical and electronic access controls, and strict rules regarding the access and use of data on our system. However, please be aware that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and we are unable to guarantee the absolute security of information we have collected from you. 

### Other Information:

### Non-Identifiable Data:

When you interact with Pioneer Works through the Services, we receive and store certain personally non-identifiable information. Such information, which is collected passively using various technologies, cannot presently be used to specifically identify you. Pioneer Works may store such information itself or such information may be included in databases owned and maintained by Pioneer Works affiliates, agents or service providers. The Services may use such information and pool it with other information to track, for example, the total number of visitors to our Site, the number of visitors to each page of our Site, and the domain names of our visitors' Internet service providers. It is important to note that no Personal Data is available or used in this process. 

### Cookies:

In operating the Services, we use a technology called "cookies." A cookie is a piece of information that the computer that hosts our Services gives to your browser when you access the Services. Our cookies help provide additional functionality to the Services and help us analyze Services usage more accurately. For instance, our Services may set a cookie on your browser that allows you to access the Services without needing to remember and then enter a password more than once during a visit to the Services. In all cases in which we use cookies, we will not collect Personal Data except with your permission. 

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system. 

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. In addition, cookies allow the website to remember any choices you make about the website (such as changes to text size, customized pages) or enable services that you have selected. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can obtain more information about cookies by visiting [http://www.allaboutcookies.org.](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/)

### The Cookies We Use:

Functionality / Preference / User Experience Cookies:

Functionality Cookies, which include preference and user experience related cookies, are used to provide services or to remember choices you make so we can personalize our content for you (for example, by remembering your user name, choice of language, schedule preferences). Our use of Functionality Cookies includes remembering preferences you have chosen to customize your experience of our Website or providing live chat functionality to you across our Websites through Intercom, ZenDesk or other similar services. These cookies last until removed by your browser. 

Analytical Cookies:

We use cookies to analyze user activity in order to improve Homebase. For example, we can use cookies to look at use of different sections of Homebase and aggregate patterns based on actions that you might perform. We can use such analysis to gain insights about how to improve the functionality and user experience of Homebase. 

Testing and Performance Improvement Cookies:

We use cookies to ensure users receive a consistent user experience while we conduct A/B testing on certain aspects of our Site in order to improve our product offerings. We also use cookies to improve the performance and reliability of our Site. 

Marketing Cookies:

We may use cookies from third-party partners such as Google and Facebook for marketing purposes. These cookies allow us to display promotional material to you on other sites you visit across the Internet. We may also share information about your behavior on the Site with third parties (including operators of third-party websites and/or social networking sites) in order to show you targeted advertisements and other content that has been customized for you. 

Google Analytics Cookies:

Name: _ga

Type: First Party Persistent

Duration: 2 years from set/update

Purpose: This cookie is typically written to the browser upon the first visit. If the cookie has been deleted by the browser operator, and the browser subsequently visits our site, a new _ga cookie is written with a different unique ID. In most cases, this cookie is used to determine unique visitors to our site and it is updated with each page view. Additionally, this cookie is provided with a unique ID that Google Analytics uses to ensure both the validity and accessibility of the cookie as an extra security measure. 

Name: _gat

Type: First Party Persistent

Duration: 24 hours from set/update

Purpose: This cookie is typically written to the browser upon the first visit. If the cookie has been deleted by the browser operator, and the browser subsequently visits our site, a new _gat cookie is written with a different unique ID. In most cases, this cookie is used to determine unique visitors to our site and it is updated with each page view. Additionally, this cookie is provided with a unique ID that Google Analytics uses to ensure both the validity and accessibility of the cookie as an extra security measure. 

Name: _utma

Type: First Party Persistent

Duration: 2 years from set/update

Purpose: This cookie is typically written to the browser upon the first visit. If the cookie has been deleted by the browser operator, and the browser subsequently visits our site, a new __utma cookie is written with a different unique ID. In most cases, this cookie is used to determine unique visitors to our site and it is updated with each page view. Additionally, this cookie is provided with a unique ID that Google Analytics uses to ensure both the validity and accessibility of the cookie as an extra security measure. 

Name: _utmb

Type: First Party Persistent

Duration: 30 minutes from set/update

Purpose: This cookie is used to establish and continue a user session with our site. When a user views a page on our site, the Google Analytics code attempts to update this cookie. If it does not find the cookie, a new one is written and a new session is established. Each time a user visits a different page on our site; this cookie is updated to expire in 30 minutes, thus continuing a single session for as long as user activity continues within 30-minute intervals. This cookie expires when a user pauses on a page on our site for longer than 30 minutes. 

Name: _utmc

Type: First Party Session

Duration: At the end of the session

Purpose: This cookie operates in conjunction with the '_utmb' cookie to determine whether or not to establish a new session for the user. If it does not find the cookie, a new one is written and a new session is established. This cookie expires when a user's session is no longer active.

Name: _utmz

Type: First Party Persistent

Duration: 6 months from set/update

Purpose: This cookie stores the type of referral used by the visitor to reach our site, whether via a direct method, a referring link, a website search, or a campaign such as an ad or an email link. It is used to calculate search engine traffic, ad campaigns and page navigation within our site. The cookie is updated with each page view to our site 

### Opting Out of Cookie Usage:

If you want to control which cookies you accept, you can configure your browser to accept all cookies or to alert you every time a cookie is offered by a website's server. Most browsers automatically accept cookies. You can set your browser option so that you will not receive cookies and you can also delete existing cookies from your browser. You may find that some parts of the site will not function properly if you have refused cookies. On most web browsers, you will find a “help” section on the toolbar. Please refer to this section for information on how to receive notification when you are receiving a new cookie and how to turn cookies off. We recommend that you leave cookies turned on because they allow you to take advantage of some of the Service features. 

### Aggregated Personal Data:

In an ongoing effort to better understand and serve the users of the Services, Pioneer Works often conducts research on its customer demographics, interests and behavior based on the Personal Data and other information provided to us. This research may be compiled and analyzed on an aggregate basis, and Pioneer Works may share this aggregate data with its affiliates, agents and business partners. This aggregate information does not identify you personally. Pioneer Works may also disclose aggregated user statistics in order to describe our services to current and prospective business partners, and to other third parties for other lawful purposes. 

### Our Use of Your Personal Data and Other Information:

Pioneer Works uses the Personal Data you provide in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy. If you provide Personal Data for a certain reason, we may use the Personal Data in connection with the reason for which it was provided. For instance, if you contact us by email, we will use the Personal Data you provide to answer your question or resolve your problem. Also, if you provide Personal Data in order to obtain access to the Services, we will use your Personal Data to provide you with access to such services and to monitor your use of such services. Pioneer Works and its subsidiaries and affiliates (the “Pioneer Works Related Companies”) may also use your Personal Data and other personally non-identifiable information collected through the Services to help us improve the content and functionality of the Services, to better understand our users and to improve the Services. Pioneer Works and its affiliates may use this information to contact you in the future to tell you about services we believe will be of interest to you. If we do so, each marketing communication we send you will contain instructions permitting you to "opt-out" of receiving future marketing communications. In addition, if at any time you wish not to receive any future marketing communications or you wish to have your name deleted from our mailing lists, please contact us as indicated below. 

### Our Disclosure of Your Personal Data and Other Information:

Pioneer Works is not in the business of selling your information. We consider this information to be a vital part of our relationship with you. There are, however, certain circumstances in which we may share your Personal Data with certain third parties without further notice to you, as set forth below: 

  * **Business Transfers:**  As we develop our business, we might sell or buy businesses or assets. In the event of a corporate sale, merger, reorganization, dissolution or similar event, Personal Data may be part of the transferred assets. 
  * **Related Companies:**  We may also share your Personal Data with our Related Companies for purposes consistent with this Privacy Policy. 
  * **Agents, Consultants and Related Third Parties:**  Pioneer Works, like many businesses, sometimes hires other companies to perform certain business-related functions. Examples of such functions include mailing information, maintaining databases and processing payments. When we employ another entity to perform a function of this nature, we only provide them with the information that they need to perform their specific function. 
  * **Legal Requirements:** Pioneer Works may disclose your Personal Data if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to (i) comply with a legal obligation, (ii) protect and defend the rights or property of Pioneer Works, (iii) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of the Services or the public, or (iv) protect against legal liability. 

### Exclusions:

This Privacy Policy does not apply to any Personal Data collected by Pioneer Works other than Personal Data collected through the Services. This Privacy Policy shall not apply to any unsolicited information you provide to Pioneer Works through the Services or through any other means. This includes, but is not limited to, information posted to any public areas of the Services, such as forums, any ideas for new products or modifications to existing products, and other unsolicited submissions (collectively, “Unsolicited Information”). All Unsolicited Information shall be deemed to be non-confidential and Pioneer Works shall be free to reproduce, use, disclose, and distribute such Unsolicited Information to others without limitation or attribution. 

### Children:

Pioneer Works does not knowingly collect Personal Data from children under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, please do not submit any Personal Data through the Services. We encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their children’s Internet usage and to help enforce our Privacy Policy by instructing their children never to provide Personal Data on the Services without their permission. If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 13 has provided Personal Data to Pioneer Works through the Services, please contact us, and we will endeavor to delete that information from our databases. 

### California Privacy Rights:

We will not share any Personal Data with third-parties for their direct marketing purposes to the extent prohibited by California law. If our practices change, we will do so in accordance with applicable laws and will notify you in advance. 

California law requires that operators of websites and online services disclose how they respond to a Do Not Track signal. Some browsers have incorporated “Do Not Track” features. Most of these features, when turned on, send a signal or preference to the website or online service that a user visits, indicating that the user does not wish to be tracked. Because there is not yet a common understanding of how to interpret Do Not Track signals, we do not currently respond to Do Not Track signal. 

### Links to Other Web Sites:

This Privacy Policy applies only to the Services. The Services may contain links to other web sites not operated or controlled by Pioneer Works (the “Third Party Sites”). The policies and procedures we described here do not apply to the Third Party Sites. The links from the Services do not imply that Pioneer Works endorses or has reviewed the Third Party Sites. We suggest contacting those sites directly for information on their privacy policies. 

### Security:

Pioneer Works takes reasonable steps to protect the Personal Data provided via the Services from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. However, no Internet or email transmission is ever fully secure or error free. In particular, email sent to or from the Services may not be secure. Therefore, you should take special care in deciding what information you send to us via email. Please keep this in mind when disclosing any Personal Data to Pioneer Works via the Internet.  As mentioned above, please be aware that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and we are unable to guarantee the absolute security of information we have collected from you 

### Other Terms and Conditions:

Your access to and use of the Services is subject to the Terms of Service at JoinHomebase.com/Terms

### Changes to Pioneer Works’ Privacy Policy:

The Services and our business may change from time to time. As a result, at times it may be necessary for Pioneer Works to make changes to this Privacy Policy. Pioneer Works reserves the right to update or modify this Privacy Policy at any time and from time to time without prior notice. Please review this policy periodically, and especially before you provide any Personal Data. This Privacy Policy was last updated on the date indicated above. Your continued use of the Services after any changes or revisions to this Privacy Policy shall indicate your agreement with the terms of such revised Privacy Policy. 

### Access and Retention of Data:

To keep your Personal Data accurate, current, and complete, or to remove your Personal Data, please contact us as specified below. We will take reasonable steps to update, remove or correct Personal Data in our possession that you have previously submitted via the Services. 

We respect your privacy rights and provide you with reasonable access to the Personal Data that you may have provided through your use of the Services. If you wish to access or amend any other Personal Data we hold about you, or to request that we delete or transfer any information about you that we have obtained from an Integrated Service, you may contact us at help@joinhomebase.com. At your request, we will have any reference to you deleted or blocked in our database. 

You may update, correct, or delete your Account information and preferences at any time by accessing your Account settings page on the Service. Please note that while any changes you make will be reflected in active user databases instantly or within a reasonable period of time, we may retain all information you submit for backups, archiving, prevention of fraud and abuse, analytics, satisfaction of legal obligations, or where we otherwise reasonably believe that we have a legitimate reason to do so. If we receive a request under this provision, we will acknowledge it within seventy-two (72) business hours and handle it in most cases within thirty (30) days. 

You may decline to share certain Personal Data with us, in which case we may not be able to provide to you some of the features and functionality of the Service. 

At any time, you may object to the processing of your Personal Data, on legitimate grounds, except if otherwise permitted by applicable law. If you believe your right to privacy granted by applicable data protection laws has been infringed upon, please contact help@joinhomebase.com. You also have a right to lodge a complaint with data protection authorities. There may be limitations or delays in our ability to take the actions listed in this section as priority will be provided to users or visitors that are residents of a country where we have a legal requirement to act on the request within a certain period of time. 

### Contacting Pioneer Works:

Please also feel free to contact us if you have any questions about Pioneer Works’ Privacy Policy or the information practices of the Services.

You may contact us as follows:  [help@joinhomebase.com.](mailto:help@joinhomebase.com)

You may also send us a written notice to:

Pioneer Works 

Attn: Privacy Officer 

425 2nd St Suite 450 

San Francisco, CA 94107
